gofreebies.com 2017-12-17

# Privacy Policy - GoFreebies.com

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy sets out how Digital Branding, LLC, operator of this website, GoFreebies.com, and other affiliated (present and future) websites (collectively, “Our Websites”) uses and protect any information that you give to any of Our Websites, including this website, when you use any of Our Websites. By using Our Websites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use Our Websites. By accessing or using any of Our Websites, including this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. The date of the last update is at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using any of Our Websites, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. This policy is effective from and was last updated on the date posted, at the bottom of this page. 

**What we collect**  
We may collect the following information about you: 

  * Name 
  * Email address 
  * Demographic information such as postal address, phone number(s), gender, birth date, preferences and interests. 
  * Site usage information such as searches, offer clicks, offer votes 
  * Other information you may voluntarily provide to us when you communicate with us. 
  * Additional information may include, but not be limited to, health and lifestyle information about you and your family such as marital status and household information (spouse, children, pets, etc.), ethnicity, education, income, occupation, purchasing habits, reading habits, insurance, participation in research surveys and clinical trials. If you communicate with us by e-mail or completing surveys, we may collect any information you share. We also may collect information such as the identification of the server your computer is logged onto and whether you opened an e-mail delivered to you by one of Our Websites or partners. 
  * In some instances we may include certain links in our e-mails that will allow us to monitor whether you access specific content or advertisements contained in that e-mail. When you click on one of these links, we will record that click and certain activities on the Web page associated with that link. 

**What we do with the information we collect**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * We may use the information for internal record keeping and administrative functions. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may send you targeted advertising via e-mail or postal mail 
  * We may share the information you provide to this Website or Digital Branding, LLC with our other affiliated websites, in other words, Our Websites 
  * We may contact you for feedback and surveys via email. 
  * We may send you general and administrative information about Our Websites via email. 
  * We may share the information you provide at registration with a trusted partner, who may display a sponsored advertisement to you during the registration process. If you choose not to accept the offer, your information is not supposed to be used any further by this partner. If you choose to accept the offer, the advertiser may collect further information from you. Such information collection would be pursuant to the partner’s privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy. 
  * We may provide your contact information to our marketing partners whose offer(s) you have selected to receive in order for them to send you special offers via email, telemarketing and direct mail. 
  * We may provide your information to other companies and individuals we hire to perform certain functions on our behalf. These companies and individuals may include but are not limited to fulfillment services and email providers. These agents have access to member personal information as needed to perform their functions. 
  * We may pass your information to a third party in the URL of a link that you click from Our Websites, to improve your experience with that third party website. Your information is not supposed to be recorded or used by the third party except to improve your experience on that website, unless you direct the website to record or use that information otherwise. You should take note of the privacy policies on these websites and ensure that they are using your information responsibly. 
  * We may use your information for various purposes, such as to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior in and to our e-mail advertisements and content, and to better understand and serve you. 

**Security**  
We are committed to taking actions to help ensure your information is secure. While no method is 100 percent secure, in order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place what we believe are suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to help safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to Our Websites. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on Our Websites. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. If we have given you (or where you have chosen) a username and password for access to certain parts of Our Websites, you are responsible for keeping these credentials confidential.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which Our Websites you visit may place on your computer's hard drive. When the file is added, the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets us know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve Our Websites in order to tailor Our Websites to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better experience when you are using any of Our Websites, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us or as described here. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Do Not Track**  
Some web browsers may give you the ability to enable a “do not track” setting that sends a special signal to the websites you encounter while web browsing. This is different form disabling certain forms of tracking by declining cookies in your browser settings, as browsers with the “do not track” setting enabled still have the ability to accept cookies. We do not respond to web browser “do not track” signals at this time. If we do so in the future, we will describe how we do so in this Privacy Policy. Our Websites may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave Our Websites, you should note that we do not have any control over the content of other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applicable to the website in question.  
For more information about "do not track" visit <https://allaboutdnt.com/> or <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

**Advertisements on Our Websites**  
You may encounter third party advertisements on Our Websites via text links, standard banner advertisements, or other forms of advertising. When engaging with these ads, you will be accepting the privacy policy of each of the advertiser websites that you click out to. We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applicable to the website you are using. Any transactions you engage in with these third party sites are independent of Our Websites. Should you have any issues with these third party sites, please contact them directly. You have the option to opt out from our newsletter and promotional emails from us by clicking here. You may also opt-out from certain “interest-based” advertising pursuant to a voluntary, industry program offered by certain advertisers. To do so, visit the following URL: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

  * You may choose not to receive our newsletter. To do so, you may opt out here. You will also be opted out of our daily prize drawing. 
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us here. You may also automatically opt out here. 

We may release your personal information to third parties if we are required by law to do so such as when we are required to provide your information in response to a subpoena, warrant, or court order, in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, or other legal action; as otherwise required by law or regulation; or if we reasonably believe it is necessary to protect our company, its customers, or the public, or to enforce our terms of service or this Privacy Policy. We may also sell, distribute, lease or transfer your personal information to third parties in connection with a corporate transaction involving us, such as a merger, acquisition, reorganization or other transaction involving us or Our Websites. We may also use, disclose or share your information, including personal information, to respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another.

We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen by opting-into receiving such information. 

We want to help you keep your personal information we hold accurate. To view or edit your personal information that has been stored online by us, please contact us at the address below. 

If you have questions about your personal information or this Privacy Policy, including any issues concerning the accuracy of your personal information, please contact us at: 

Digital Branding, LLC   
20 Jay Street, Ste. 502   
Brooklyn, NY 11201   
Email: support@gofreebies.com   

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above contacts. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Removal**   
To remove your name from our list, contact us and we will be happy to unsubscribe you from our system. Please note that you will no longer receive our offerings by email when you do this. 

**Children Under the Age of 13**   
Our Websites are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 should provide any information to or on Our Websites. Our Websites are intended only for users 18 years of age and over. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on Our Websites or on or through any of the features or register on Our Websites, make any purchases through Our Websites, use any of the interactive or public comment features of Our Websites or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screenname or username you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@gofreebies.com. 

Last updated: February 25, 2016
